//  class Questions
//  {  
   final questionList = const [   
                      {
                        'questionText':'When do you feel at your best?',
                        'answer':[  {'text':'in the morning','score':2},
                                    {'text':'during the afternoon and early evening','score':4},
                                    {'text':'late at night','score':6}],
                      }, //question 1

                      {'questionText':'You usually walk....',
                        'answer':[  {'text':'fairly fast, with long steps','score':6},
                                    {'text':'fairly fast, with little steps','score':4},
                                    {'text':'less fast head up, looking the world in the face','score':7},
                                    {'text':'less fast, head down','score':2},
                                    {'text':'very slowly','score':1}],
                      },//Question 2
                        
                      { 'questionText':'When talking to people, you...',
                        'answer':[  {'text':'stand with your arms folded','score':4},
                                    {'text':'have your hands clasped','score':2},
                                    {'text':'have one or both your hands on your hips or in pockets','score':5},
                                    {'text':'touch or push the person to whom you are talking','score':7},
                                    {'text':'play with your ear, touch your chin or smooth your hair','score':6}],
                      },//Question 3
                        
                      { 'questionText':'When relaxing, you sit with...',
                        'answer':[  {'text':'your knees bent with your legs neatly side by side','score':4},
                                    {'text':'your legs crossed','score':6},
                                    {'text':'your legs stretched out or straight','score':2},
                                    {'text':'one leg curled under you','score':1}],
                      },//Question 4
                                                
                      { 'questionText':'When something really amuses you, You react with...',
                        'answer':[  {'text':'a big appreciated laugh','score':6},
                                    {'text':'a laugh, but not a loud one','score':4},
                                    {'text':'a quiet chuckle','score':3},
                                    {'text':'a sheepish smile','score':5}],
                      },//Question 5

                      { 'questionText':'When you go to a party or social gathering, you...',
                        'answer':[  {'text':'make a loud entrance so everyone notices you','score':6},
                                    {'text':'make a quiet entrance, looking around for someone you know','score':4},
                                    {'text':'make the quietest entrance, trying to stay unnoticed','score':2}],
                      },// Question 6
                        
                      { 'questionText':'When you’re working or concentrating very hard, and you’re interrupted, you...',
                        'answer':[  {'text':'welcome the break','score':6},
                                    {'text':'feel extremely irritated','score':2},
                                    {'text':'vary between these two extremes','score':4}],
                      },//Question 7
                        
                      { 'questionText':'Which of the following colors do you like most?',
                        'answer':[  {'text':'Red or orange','score':6},
                                    {'text':'black','score':7},
                                    {'text':'yellow or light blue','score':5},
                                    {'text':'green','score':4},
                                    {'text':'dark blue or purple','score':3},
                                    {'text':'white','score':2},
                                    {'text':'brown or gray','score':1},],
                      },//Question 8
                        
                      { 'questionText':'When you are in bed at night, in those last few moments before going to sleep, you lie...',
                        'answer':[  {'text':'stretched out on your back','score':7},
                                    {'text':'stretched out face down on your stomach','score':6},
                                    {'text':'on your side, slightly curled','score':4},
                                    {'text':'with your head on one arm','score':2},
                                    {'text':'with your head under the covers','score':1}],
                      },//Question 9
                        
                      { 'questionText':'You often dream that you are...',
                        'answer':[  {'text':'falling','score':4},
                                    {'text':'fighting or struggling','score':2},
                                    {'text':'searching for something or somebody','score':3},
                                    {'text':'flying or floating','score':5},
                                    {'text':'you usually have dreamless sleep','score':6},
                                    {'text':'your dreams are always pleasant','score':1},],
                      },//Question 10
                        
                      // { 'questionText':'What\'s your favourite colour?',
                      //   'answer':[  {'text':'Black','score':2},
                      //               {'text':'Black','score':2},
                      //               {'text':'Black','score':2},
                      //               {'text':'Black','score':2}],
                      // },//Question 11
                        
                      // { 'questionText':'What\'s your favourite colour?',
                      //   'answer':[  {'text':'Black','score':2},
                      //               {'text':'Black','score':2},
                      //               {'text':'Black','score':2},
                      //               {'text':'Black','score':2}],
                      // },//Question 12
                        
                      // { 'questionText':'What\'s your favourite colour?',
                      //   'answer':[  {'text':'Black','score':2},
                      //               {'text':'Black','score':2},
                      //               {'text':'Black','score':2},
                      //               {'text':'Black','score':2}],
                      // },//Question 13
                        
                      // { 'questionText':'What\'s your favourite colour?',
                      //   'answer':[  {'text':'Black','score':2},
                      //               {'text':'Black','score':2},
                      //               {'text':'Black','score':2},
                      //               {'text':'Black','score':2}],
                      // },//Question 14
                        
                      // { 'questionText':'What\'s your favourite colour?',
                      //   'answer':[  {'text':'Black','score':2},
                      //               {'text':'Black','score':2},
                      //               {'text':'Black','score':2},
                      //               {'text':'Black','score':2}],
                      // },//Question 15
                        
                    ];
 
//  List<Map<String, Object>> questionSetter()
//  {
//    return questionList;
//  }
 
//  }